A Guide to the Papers of William H. Kennon, 1808-1903
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of William H. Kennon 1808-1903
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
38-95
This collection consists of ca. 950 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The collection was deposited in 1932 by the Rev. William Henry Laird who was acting for Mr. Charles R. Kennon. The collection was made a gift to the Library in December 1980, by Charles R. Kennon, JR., and Richard R. Kennon of Powhatan, Virginia.
Scope and Content Information
The Kennon family papers, 1808-1903, consist of ca. 950 items which are chiefly of William H. Kennon, Beverley Randolph, Nancy Randolph Kennon Selden, Miles C. Selden, Charles Randolph Kennon and William Upshur Kennon, pertaining to management of family plantation, Norwood (Powhatan County, Va.), and estate settlements.
Topics also include family and social matters, the courtship of Nancy Randolph and William H. Kennon and her father's objections, William H. Kennon's naval career, a lawsuit (Kennon vs. Wilkinson), a fugitive slave (1841), and mention of Beverley Kennon's death in U.S.S. Princeton accident (1844).
The papers also include correspondence, 1830-1840, of Beverley Randolph to his son, Charles H. Randolph, pertaining to Charles' studies at the University of Virginia and the University of Paris, including one letter referring briefly to the riot at the University of Virginia (1831).
Of interest are a letter, 1861, to Nancy Randolph Kennon Selden from Landonia Randolph concerning family matters, slavery, and secession; two letters, 1861, pertaining to the requested return of a hired slave; letters, 1862-1865, of William Upshur Kennon and Charles Randolph Kennon to their mother concerning camp life, including one letter mentioning a slave at the front.
There is aslo correspondence, 1875-1883, of William Upshur Kennon, acting plantation manager for James Murray of England, owner of Bendover plantation, Goochland County, Va., pertaining to agricultural concerns, plantation management and sales of livestock and wheat, including a crop rotation plan (1879); and farm journal, ca. 1880, of William Upshur Kennon.
There is also a letter, 1824, from Abel Upshur concerning William H. Kennon's naval career and social life and celebrations honoring Lafayette; letter, 1837, from John Hartwell Cocke offering his consolations; letter, 1840, from James Kirke Paulding accepting William H. Kennon's resignation; and a receipt and letter, 1842, of Thomas Mann Randolph pertaining to sale of cattle.
Also present is a plantation journal, 1808, of Beverley Randolph including slave records; six bank books, 1822-1832, of Beverley Randolph; one bank book, 1827-1828, of John Heth; farm journal, 1840-1842, of W. A. Kennon; two time books, 1873-1883; four farm books, 1873-1883, including freedmen's accounts; balance book, 1887-1903; and two bank books, 1897-1903, of William Upshur Kennon.
The colleciton also includes a catalog, 1866, of the private library at Norwood.
Arrangement
The papers have been arranged chronologically in five boxes and some volumes have been shelved separately in the ledger stacks.
Contents List
- T. C. Gillie to William W. Kennon 1817 November 14 (Box 1)
- C. Stewart to William W. Kennon 1819 November 15 (Box 1)
- R. Henley to William Kennon 1821 October 29 (Box 1)
- A. Sinclair to William H. Kennon 1822 June 4 (Box 1)
- Smith Thompson to William H. Kennon 1822 June 11 (Box 1)
- J. R. Poinsett to William H. Kennon 1823 February 13 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to J. R. Poinsett 1823 February 19 (Box 1)
- C. Freeman to William H. Kennon 1823 March 8 (Box 1)
- Smith Thompson to William H. Kennon 1823 March 27 (Box 1)
- Henry Gibson to George P. Upshur (copy) 1823 July 12 (Box 1)
- George P. Upshur to Henry Gibson (copy) 1823 July 20 (Box 1)
- Henry Gibson to George P. Upshur (copy) 1823 August 6 (Box 1)
- George P. Upshur to Henry Gibson (copy) 1823 August 30 (Box 1)
- Henry Gibson to George P. Upshur (copy) 1823 September 10 (Box 1)
- George P. Upshur to Henry Gibson 1823 September 30 (Box 1)
- H. Clark to William H. Kennon 1823 November 14 (Box 1)
- S.L. Southard to W. H. Kennon 1823 November 15 (Box 1)
- B.F. Stocteton to William H. Kennon 1823 November 29 (Box 1)
- Thos. Green to William H. Kennon 1824 Jan 3 (Box 1)
- Lieut. Percival to William Kennon 1824 April 20 (Box 1)
- M. B. C. to Nancy Randolph 1824 May 16 (Box 1)
- George P. Upshur to Isaac Hull 1824 July 20 (Box 1)
- George P. Upshur to James Armstrong 1824 July 21 (Box 1)
- Abel Upshur to William H. Kennon 1824 September 29 (Box 1)
- Receipt - William Kennon To D. Fernandez 1824 October 9 (Box 1)
- William Kennon to William W. Ramsay 1824 October 14 (Box 1)
- William Kennon to John Percival 1825 February 23 (Box 1)
- James Percival to William Kennon 1825 February 23 (Box 1)
- William Kennon to James Percival 1825 February 24 (Box 1)
- Isaac Hull to William Kennon 1825 March 2 (Box 1)
- James Kennon to James Percival 1825 March 24 (Box 1)
- William Kennon to James Percival (copy) 1825 March 24 (Box 1)
- George P. Upshur to William Kennon 1825 April 18 (Box 1)
- [?] to William H. Kennon ca. 1825 (Box 1)
- Beverly Kennon to William Kennon 1826 August 25 (Box 1)
- William Kennon to [?] Ely 1826 August 29 (Box 1)
- S. L. Munford to William Kennon 1827 April 10 (Box 1)
- MS Poem by William Harwood 1827 October 20 (Box 1)
- J. Chauncey to William Kennon 1827 October 29 (Box 1)
- Watson to William H. Kennon 1827 December 22 (Box 1)
- Watson to William H. Kennon 1828 April 18 (Box 1)
- C. Jones to William H. Kennon 1828 November 19 (Box 1)
- George P. Upshur to William H. Kennon 1829 Jan 10 (Box 1)
- George P. Upshur to William H. Kennon 1829 March 20 (Box 1)
- John C. Carter to William H. Kennon 1829 April 23 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to L. Warrington 1829 May 22 (Box 1)
- George W. Munford to William H. Kennon 1829 August 1 (Box 1)
- R. B. Randolph to William H. Kennon 1829 September 5 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous 1829 (Box 1)
- N. Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1830? Jan 25 (Box 1)
- Harriet Heth to Charles H. Randolph 1830? February 13 (Box 1)
- [E. S.?] Kennon to William H. Kennon 1830 March 4 (Box 1)
- Elizabeth Kennon to William H. Kennon 1830 March 20 (Box 1)
- Cathrine E. Kennon to William H. Kennon 1830 May 7 (Box 1)
- William Vincent to William H. Kennon 1830 May 8 (Box 1)
- Harriet C. Heth to Charles H. Randolph 1830? June 10 (Box 1)
- William Kennon to John Gallegar 1830 June 23 (Box 1)
- [E. S.?] to William H. Kennon 1830 July 29 (Box 1)
- R. Kennon to William H. Kennon 1830 August 20 (Box 1)
- R. Kennon to William H. Kennon 1830 September 11 (Box 1)
- George S. Kennon to William H. Kennon 1830 September 15 (Box 1)
- N. Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1803 September 22 (Box 1)
- Georgeanna Bush Kennon to William H. Kennon 1830 September 27 (Box 1)
- Beverly Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1830 November 1 (Box 1)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1830 November 1 (Box 1)
- N. Randolph to Charles H. Randolph ca.1830 December 9 (Box 1)
- C. H. Randolph to William Kennon ca.1830 (Box 1)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1831 April 7 (Box 1)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1831 April 27 (Box 1)
- Harriet Heth to Charles H. Kennon ca.1831 May 2 (Box 1)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles Randolph ( UVa riot) 1831 June 10 (Box 1)
- Landon[?] to [William H. Kennon?] 1831 July 14 (Box 1)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1831 September 23 (Box 1)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1831 October 30 (Box 1)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1832 March 1 (Box 1)
- William Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 March 16 (Box 1)
- William H. Randolph to Charles S. Gray 1832 March 30 (Box 1)
- William H. Randolph to Charles S. Gray 1832 April 1 (Box 1)
- Bevy. Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1832 April 2 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Charles S. Gray 1832 April 4 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 April 5 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 April 15 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 May 13 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 June 4 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 June 5 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 June 7 (Box 1)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1832 June 19 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 June 27 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 August 12 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 August 20 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 August 28 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 September 10 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 September 12 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 September 15 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 September 18 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 September 25 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon to Nancy Randolph 1832 September 29 (Box 1)
- [?] to William H. Kennon ca.1832 (Box 1)
- William H. Kennon - Receipts 1832 (Box 1)
- ca.1833 (Box 1)
- [?] Jones to William H. KennonMary Anne to Nancy Randolph 1834 July 18 (Box 1)
- [?] Jones to William H. Kennon 1834 July 24 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous receipts, household furnishings 1833 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous receipts, household furnishings 1834 (Box 1)
- R. Kennon to William H. Kennon ca.1835 April 16 (Box 1)
- C.H. Randolph to William H. Kennon 1835 May 8 (Box 1)
- E. B. Sinclair to Nancy Kennon ca.1835 (Box 1)
- Receipts, Clothing Miscellaneous 1835 (Box 2)
- M. Heth to William H. Kennon ca.1835 (Box 2)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1836 May 18 (Box 2)
- Beverley Randolph to Charles Randolph 1836 March 16 (Box 2)
- M. Dickerson to William H. Kennon 1836 June 4 (Box 2)
- Nancy Kennon to William H. Kennon ca.1836 (Box 2)
- Receipts, clothing, miscellaneous 1836 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to Nancy 1837 Jan 9 (Box 2)
- William H. Gordon to William H. Kennon 1837 Jan 12 (Box 2)
- William B. Subrick to William H. Kennon 1837 February 17 (Box 2)
- John H Cocke to William H Kennon 1837 April 14 (Box 2)
- G. P. Upshur ro William H. Kennon 1837 April 15 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to William H. Kennon 1837 June 6 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to William H. Kennon 1837 June 15 (Box 2)
- L. F. L. to Charles Randolph 1837 June 25 (Box 2)
- B. Baylor to William H. Kennon 1837 July 1 (Box 2)
- Louisa H. Deas to Mrs. William Kennon 1837 July 19 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to William H. Kennon 1837 July 26 (Box 2)
- Landon[?] to Mrs. W. Kennon 1837 August 3 (Box 2)
- Louisa H. Deas to Mrs. William Kennon 1837 August 18 (Box 2)
- Beverley Randolph to William H. Kennon 1837 September 1 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous 1837 (Box 2)
- Beverley Randolph to William H Kennon 1838 Jan 30 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to Lt. William H. Kennon 1838 December 9 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1838 (Box 2)
- William W. Kennon to Mrs. William H. Kennon 1839 March 11 (Box 2)
- Beverley Randolph to William H. Kennon 1839 June 10 (Box 2)
- T. T. Naper to William H. Kennon 1839 August 4 (Box 2)
- [?] Chauncey to Geo. L. Kennon 1839 August 28 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1839 (Box 2)
- C. Bartlett to William H. Kennon 1840 Jan 10 (Box 2)
- Power of Attorney to William H. Kennon from C. H. Randolph 1840 March 21 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to William H. Kennon 1840 March 31 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to William H. Kennon ca.1840 April 9 (Box 2)
- C. E. W. To Mrs. Nancy Kennon ca.1840 April 14 (Box 2)
- F. Selma Buchanan to William H Randolph 1840 April 20 (Box 2)
- Contract for overseer for "Norwood" 1840 May 8 (Box 2)
- D. C. Randolph to William H. Kennon 1840 May 18 (Box 2)
- Nancy Kennon to Charles H. Randolph ca.1840 August 8 (Box 2)
- J. K. Paulding to William H. Kennon 1840 December 16 (Box 2)
- D. W. Giraud to William H. Kennon 1840 December 19 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1840 (Box 2)
- R. Kennon to Beverley Kennon ca.1840 (Box 2)
- Sidnum Grady to William H. Kennon 1841 Jan 19 (Box 2)
- Contract for overseer of "Norwood" 1841 March 1 (Box 2)
- George Nicolson Johnson to William H. Kennon 1841 June 5 (Box 2)
- H. A. Deas to William H. Kennon 1841 September 25 (Box 2)
- Fitz Allen Deas to William H. Kennon 1841 October 6 (Box 2)
- McKean Buchanan to William H. Kennon 1841 November 11 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1841 (Box 2)
- Hill Carter to William H. Kennon 1842 Jan 7 (Box 2)
- Hill Carter to William H. Kennon 1842 Jan 15 (Box 2)
- Th. Randolph to [?] Finley 1842 February 9 (Box 2)
- Robert Gwastmey to William H. Kennon 1842 February 10 (Box 2)
- McKean Buchanan to William H. Kennon 1842 March 14 (Box 2)
- W. K. Mayo to William H. Kennon 1842 June 18 (Box 2)
- S. Edwards to Fred K. Eagle 1842 August 12 (Box 2)
- Haxall Bros. & Co. to William H. Kennon 1842 August 13 (Box 2)
- F. Engle to William H. Kennon 1842 August 20 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to William H. 1842 September 13Kennon (Box 2)
- Th. Randolph to William H. Kennon 1842 October 1 (Box 2)
- W. M. Harrison to William H. Kennon 1842 October 13 (Box 2)
- John B. Chapman to William H. Kennon 1842 October 16 (Box 2)
- [?]Forrest to William H. Kennon 1842 November 21 (Box 2)
- Thos. H. Harris to [?] Kennon 1842 December 13 (Box 2)
- [?] to [?] 1842 December 25 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Bills and Receipts 1842 (Box 2)
- William H. Kennon to [?] Segram 1843 Jan 16 (Box 2)
- Overseers contract with T. L. Mallory 1843 Jan 17 (Box 2)
- Hill Carter to William H. Kennon 1843 Jan 26 (Box 2)
- John S. Millson to William H. Kennon 1843 February 17 (Box 2)
- W. H. Kennon, Jr. to William H. Kennon 1843 March 5 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to William H. Kennon 1843 March 16 (Box 2)
- John Wright to William H. Kennon 1843 March 17 (Box 2)
- John Wright to William H. Kennon 1843 March 22 (Box 2)
- R. Picken tp William H. Kennon 1843 April 25 (Box 2)
- W. H. Kennon, Jr. to William H. Kennon 1843 October 10 (Box 2)
- Aunt Landenia to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1843 November 16 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Bills, Receipts and Notes 1843 (Box 2)
- Joseph W. Powell to William H. Kennon 1843 December 7 (Box 2)
- J. R. Anderson to W. William H. Kennon 1843 November 8 (Box 2)
- Beverley Kennon to George Kennon 1843 December 16 (Box 2)
- William S. Dance to George L. Kennon 1844 Jan 16 (Box 2)
- George L. Kennon to Duncalion Wilkinson 1844 February 7 (Box 2)
- George L. Kennon to Nancy Kennon 1844 February 29 (Box 2)
- Baynham Baylor to Mrs. William H. Kennon 1844 November 29 (Box 2)
- [?] to Nancy Kennon 1844 December 5? (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1844relating to estate of William H. Kennon (Box 2)
- Questions to be asked witnesses in Kennon v. Wilkinson ca. 1844? (Box 2)
- George Nicholson Johnson to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1845 Jan 16 (Box 2)
- L. Wharton to General Taylor 1845 July 2 (Box 2)
- L. J. R. to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1846 February 26 (Box 2)
- H.[?] Clairborne to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1846 March 13 (Box 2)
- W. Dandridge Kennon to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1846 March 18 (Box 2)
- George Nicholson Johnson to [?] 1847 December 18 (Box 2)
- Receipt 1848 (Box 2)
- Dan Tavart to William H. Kennon, Jr. 1849 Jan 9 (Box 2)
- Thomas Barclay to [?] Thorburn 1849 October 23 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1849 (Box 2)
- Receipt: S. Pardue to Mrs. Nancy Kennon ca.1849 (Box 2)
- Conway D. White to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1850 June 20 (Box 2)
- Miles C. Selden to [?] 1852 April 28 (Box 2)
- Account Book 1852-1853 (Box 2)
- Account Book of Mrs. Nancy Kennon Selden and Miles C. Selden 1848-1853 (Box 2)
- L. B. Mason to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1854 May 20 (Box 2)
- Charles Randolph Kennon to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1855 March (Box 2)
- Charles Randolph Kennon to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1855 Jan 26 (Box 2)
- Landonia [Randolph?] to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1857 June 26 (Box 3)
- J. G. Miller to Miles C. Selden 1857 [July?] 11 (Box 3)
- J. G. Miller to Miles C. Selden 1857 [July?] (Box 3)
- L. B. Mason to Mrs. Nancy Kennon 1857 December 16 (Box 3)
- J. A. Latane to F. Lay 1858 June 18 (Box 3)
- N. Selden (formerly Nancy Kennon) to Miles C. Selden 1859 August 5 (Box 3)
- N. Selden to Miles C. Selden 1859 August 11 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1859 August 16 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1859 August 18 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1859 August 27 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1859 November 25 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1859 November 30 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1859 December 2 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1859 December 5 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden ca. 1859? (Box 3)
- M. B. C. To [Mrs. Nancy Selden?] 1860 Jan 3 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 Jan 12 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 Jan 23 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 February 14 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. 1860 March 7Selden (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 March 10 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 March 20 (Box 3)
- Passport of Charles Randolph Kennon 1860 March 24 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 March 29 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 March 29 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 April 13 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 April 21 (Box 3)
- Miles C. Selden to Nancy Selden 1860 May 21 (Box 3)
- Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1860 June 17 (Box 3)
- M. B. C. To Mrs. Nancy Selden 1860 September 24 (Box 3)
- Landonia Randolph to Nancy Selden 1860 October 6 (Box 3)
- M. B. C. To Mrs. Nancy Selden 1860 October 22 (Box 3)
- Landonia J. Randolph to Mrs. Nancy Kennon ca.1860 (Box 3)
- M. B. C. To Mrs. Nancy Selden 1861 February 11 (Box 3)
- Landonia J. Randolph to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1861 March 19 (Box 3)
- Landonia J. Randolph to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1861 August 16 (Box 3)
- Landonia J. Randolph to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1861 September 11 (Box 3)
- Binnie to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1861 October (Box 3)
- Binnie to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1861 October (Box 3)
- Willie Selden to Mrs Nancy Selden 1861 November 24 (Box 3)
- J. Myers to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1861 December 23 (Box 3)
- J. Myers to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1862 Jan 2 (Box 3)
- Landonia J. Randolph to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1862 February 17 (Box 3)
- Nannie to [?] 1862 May 7 (Box 3)
- R. E. Mason to Nancy [?] 1862 July 22 (Box 3)
- Willie Kennon to Mrs Nancy Selden 1862 June 15 (Box 3)
- William A. Kennon to [?] 1862 October 28 (Box 3)
- William A. Kennon to [?] 1862 December 26 (Box 3)
- Charles R. Kennon to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1863 May 13 (Box 3)
- James A. Selden to Charles R. Kennon 1863 June 17 (Box 3)
- Willie H. Kennon to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1863 September 6 (Box 3)
- M. B. C. To Mrs. Nancy Selden 1864 April 21 (Box 3)
- C. R. Kennon to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1865 March 25 (Box 3)
- Caroline E. Greatmey [?] 1865 June 27 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnson to Charles R. Kennon 1865 August 1 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1867 June 22 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1867 July 6 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1868 June 5 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous letter from Georgie to [?] 186[?]? (Box 3)
- Order to repair road 1873 September 29 (Box 3)
- Miles C. Selden to Nancy Selden 1874 September 17 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Notes 1874 (Box 3)
- Memorandum Books of William Upshur Kennon [?] ca.1874 (Box 3)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry 1875 February 1 (Box 3)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry 1875 February 11 (Box 3)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry 1875 February 15 (Box 3)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry 1875 March 21 (Box 3)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry 1875 May 18 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1875 (Box 3)
- R. J. Barker & Co. To William H. Kennon 1876 February 11 (Box 3)
- William Upshur Kennon to R. J. Barker & Co. 1876 February 15 (Box 3)
- William Upshur Kennon to James Murry 1876 March 30 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1876 March 31 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Murry 1876 May 8 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1876 May 11 (Box 3)
- Hooker & Thomas to William Upshur Kennon 1876 May 19 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Murry 1876 August 5 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Murry 1876 August 24 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Murry 1876 August 26 (Box 3)
- Theodore H. Conger to W. W. Kennon 1876 November 21 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1876 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1877 July 4 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1877 July 11 (Box 3)
- Mrs. Nancy Selden to Miles C. Selden 1877 August 1 (Box 3)
- Herman Stump, Jr. to [William Upshur?] Kennon 1877 September 5 (Box 3)
- R. J. Baker & Co. to Sublett & Carr 1877 September 24 (Box 3)
- Frank Brown to William Upshur Kennon 1877 October 10 (Box 3)
- Mrs. J. B. Murry to Mrs. [William Upshur?] Kennon 1877 December 19 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Receipts, Accounts 1877 (Box 3)
- William Upshur Kennedy to James Murry 1878 April 24 (Box 3)
- E. [?] Laigh to F. W. Chiles 1878 February 1 (Box 3)
- F. W. Chiles to William Upshur Kennon 1878 February 6 (Box 3)
- F. W. Chiles to William Upshur Kennon 1878 May 5 (Box 3)
- E. M. Sedt to Mrs. William Upshur Kennon 1878 December 8 (Box 3)
- Jas. T. Othere [?] to William Upshur Kennon 1879 Jan 7 (Box 3)
- David Leyshon to William Upshur Kennon 1879 Jan 27 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1879 April 9 (Box 3)
- Howard Turniford to William Upshur Kennon 1879 April 18 (Box 3)
- Herman Stump, Jr. to Sublett & Carr 1879 May 6 (Box 3)
- James Buckingham to William Upshur Kennon 1879 May 14 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1879 May 29 (Box 3)
- Poem of [?] 1879 December 4 (Box 3)
- W. T. Walker to William 1879 December 10Upshur Kennon (Box 3)
- Plan for crop rotation for "Bendover" 1879 (Box 3)
- Account Book 1879 (Box 3)
- Receipts, clippings, accounts 1879 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1879 (Box 3)
- Certificate of Residences of Charles Kennon 187[?]? May 4 (Box 3)
- Account Book 1879? (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 Jan 4 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 February 4 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 February 13 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 March 24 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 April 14 (Box 3)
- Mary [?] to Mrs. Miles C. Selden 1880 May 1 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnston to Charles R. Kennon 1880 May 14 (Box 3)
- Lucy [Heth?] to Mrs. M. C. Selden ca.1880 May 23 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnston to C. R. Kennon 1880 May 25 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnston to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1880 May 25 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnston to C. R. Kennon 1880 June 4 (Box 3)
- William Upshur Kennon to [?]Crouch 1880 June 22 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnston to Charles R. Kennon 1880 June 26 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 July 7 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnston to Charles R. Kennon 1880 July 27 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 July 27 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 July 29 (Box 3)
- E. M. A. Heth to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1880 July 31 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 August 6 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 August 9 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 September 1 (Box 3)
- Lizzie [?]to Mrs. Nancy Selden ca.1880 September 28 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 October 14 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnston to Charles R. Murry 1880 November 8 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1880 November 24 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnston to Charles R. Murry 1880 December 9 (Box 3)
- Andrew Johnston to Charles R. Murry 1880 December 18 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Receipts 1880 (Box 3)
- Contract (copy) 1880 (Box 3)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 Jan 5 (Box 4)
- James Murry to William Upshur Kennon 1881 Jan 12 (Box 4)
- Lucy [Heth?] to Mrs. Nancy Selden 1881 February 4 (Box 4)
- Contract for ferry rights at "Norwood" 1881 February 4 (Box 4)